<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Joshua Gould on Li Lab</title>
    <link>https://lilab-cbb.github.io/authors/joshua-gould/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Joshua Gould on Li Lab</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy;2019- Bo Li</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Jul 2018 00:00:00 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://lilab-cbb.github.io/authors/joshua-gould/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>scCloud</title>
      <link>https://lilab-cbb.github.io/software/sccloud/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jul 2018 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lilab-cbb.github.io/software/sccloud/</guid>
      <description>scCloud is a cloud-based single-cell and single-nucleus RNA-Seq data analysis framework that is scalable, cost-effective, able to process a variety of data types and easily accessible to biologists. It is developed based on Google Cloud Platform and Broad Institute’s FireCloud and Terra services, and is publicly accessible. scCloud source codes contain two components. The first component consists of WDL (Workflow Description Language) files and Docker files that are required for workflow execution and listed here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>scCloudPy</title>
      <link>https://lilab-cbb.github.io/software/sccloudpy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jul 2018 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lilab-cbb.github.io/software/sccloudpy/</guid>
      <description>scCloudPy is a python package that takes gene-count matrices as input and performs a wide range of analyses, such as quality control, highly variable gene selection, batch correction, principal component analysis (PCA), k-nearest neighbor graph construction, diffusion map, clustering, t-SNE-, UMAP-, and force-directed layout-based visualization, differential expression, cluster-specific marker detection and marker-based cell type annotation.
Click here to read scCloudPy documentation
Publications:
 Manuscript in preparation.  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>